Guide to the Lee Family Papers, 1754-1836
Department of Special Collections
- ORIGINAL LETTERS AND DOCUMENTS
  - F (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - 3. 1798, Feb. 1__.N.P. [J. Ford] to Wm. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. new job, thanks for reference.
    - 4. 1799, June 3.N.P. J. Ford to [Col.] Lee. [High Wycombe] A.L.S. asks for money, wants another job, Lord Robert Seymour.
    - 5. N.D., June 12,N.P. Joseph Ford to Cornet Lee. Tunbridge Wells. A.N.S. job.
    - 6. N.D.,N.P. J. Ford to Maj. Lee. [H] enley. A.L.S. wants interest paid.
    - 7. 1796, Feb. 4.Uxbridge. R. Foster to [Lee?] N.P. [Prince of Wales] A.L.S. opening for Sergeant-major in Cinque Port Regt.
    - 8. [1795?] Jan. 6.St. James St. Robert Foster to Maj. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. pattern for sword hilt, softness of gold.
    - 9. 1795, Feb. 12.H.Q. Rheine. [H.E.] Fox to Officer commanding 16th Lt. Dragoons. Rheine. A.L.S. orders to move to Elte and Saerbeck.
    - 10. 1795, Feb. 21.H.Q. Osnaburgh. [H.E.] Fox to Officer commanding 16th Light Dragoons. Rheine. D.S. orders from Gen. Harcourt to march to Schapen and Hofsten.
    - 11. 1795, Mar. 20.Osnaburgh. [H.E.] Fox to Officer Commanding M. Gern. Sir Robert Laurie's Brigade. Logel. copy. orders from Harcourt, march route, s. Wm. Lee.
    - 12. 1798, Feb. 13.Chatham Barracks. [H.E.] Fox to Col. Calvert. N.P. A.L.S. re: Richard Steele, letter of Maj. Armstrong.
    - 13. 1786, Feb. 10.N.P. John Foxall to Cornet Lee. Canterbury. A.L.S. bill, security.
    - 14. 1792, Mar. 23.Strasbourg. P.J. Franck to M. Lee. London. A.L.S. in French. re: books sent and bill.
    - 15. 1792, [Nov.] 17.Strasbourg. P.J. Franck to M. Lee. Hartwell. A.L.S. in French. books lost?
    - 16. 1787, Aug. 1.Paris. J.G. Fraser to Wm. Lee. Stras-bourg. A.L.S. journey through Switzerland, fight, Glaciers of Savoy, wood, education, Brunswick, the pox, Desincour, women, Butter.
    - 17. 1792, June 21.London. P. Fribourg to Capt. Lee. Hartwell. A.L.S. bill.
    - 18. 1792, May 18.London. Fribourg and Freyer to Capt. Lee. London. A.L.S. outstanding bill.
    - 19. 1797, Jan. 10.Maidenhead. W.J. Fry to Maj. Lee. Henley. A.L.S. book-sling?
    - 20. 1798, Nov. 29.Kensington Barracks. W.J. Fry to Lt. Col. Lee. Windsor. A.L.S. Thanks-giving - shops closed.
  - FAWCETT, FERNANDEZ, FIOTT, FOZARD (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - 1. 1796, Mar. 1.War Office. Fawcett to Officer Commanding 16th Lt. Dragoons. St. Albans. cover only.
    - 2 & 3. 1796, Apr. 9.Adjt. Generals Office. Wm. Fawcett to Maj. Lee. Henley. L.S. and cover. two horses to be shot.
    - 4 & 5. 1796, Apr. 24.Adjt. Generals Office. Wm. Fawcett to Maj. Lee. Newbury. A.L.S. and cover. deserter.
    - 6. 1796, July 2.Adjt. Generals Office. Wm Fawcett to Gen. Harcourt. N.P. A.L.S. OKs for Duke of York, leave for Maj. Lee.
    - 7. 1796, Oct. 13.Horse Guards. Wm. Fawcett to Officer Commanding 16th Regt. of Lt. Dragoons. Reading. A.L.S. dispose of horses cost by Major. General Gwynne.
    - 8. 1798, Feb. 15.London. Wm. Fawcett to Lt. Col. Lee. Guildford. cover with free frank.
    - 9. 1798, July 9.London. Wm. Fawcett to Lt. Col. Lee. Windsor. cover with Fawcett's free frank.
    - 10. 1798, July 15.[Horse Guards] Wm. Fawcett to Lt. Col. Lee. N.P. A.N.S. enlistment of Riehard Steele [see Armstrong and Fox for mentioned enclosures]
    - 11. 1798, Dec. 24.Horse Guards. Wm. Fawcett to Lt. Col. Affleck or Officer Commanding 16th or Queens Regt. of Light Dragoons. L.S. 12th Lt. Dragoons in Portugal need horses, 16th to furnish 40, Gen. Gwyn to inspect.
    - 12. 1798, Dec. 28.Horse Guards. Wm. Fawcett to Lt. Col. Affleck. N.P. A.L.S. inspection of horses.
    - 13 & 14. 1799, Mar. 3London. S. Fernandez to Lt. Col. Lee. Windsor. A.L.S. and cover. annuities, Lord Kenyon.
    - 15. 1799, May 25.London. S. Fernandez to Lt. Col. Lee. Windsor. A.L.S. financial.
    - 16. 1799, June 29.London. S. Fernandez to Lt. Col. Lee. Sunninghell Wells. A.L.S. financial.
    - 17. Same as # 16 but directed to Windsor.
    - 18. 1799, Sept. 24.London. S. Fernandez to Lt. Col. Lee. Hartwell. A.L.S. financial.
    - 19. 1799, Oct. 24.London. S. Fernandez to Lt. Col. Lee. Hartwell. A.L.S. Mr. Rose, Mr. Allingham.
    - 20. N.D.Fleur de Lys, Winkfield. S. Fernandez to Lt. Col. Lee. Windsor. A.L.S.
    - Special packet, John Fiott to Wm. Lee Antonie.
    - 21. 1782, Aug. 13.London. John Fiott to Wm. Lee Antonie. Easton. A.L.S. personal letter to brother-in-law, launching of the Houghton, fashions, social activities.
    - 22. 1783, Feb. 24.Jersey. John Fiott to Wm. Lee Antonie. N.P. A.L.S. trip to Guernsey, privateer, Weymouth, a consumptive, a French prize, ship wrecks and salvagers, Portland.
    - 23. 1786, May 30.New Broad St. John Fiott to Wm. Lee Antonie. N.P. A.L.S. mentions Sir William.
    - 24. 1786, May 31.Harwick. John Fiott to Wm. Lee Antonie. N.P. A.L.S. Sir William and Mr. Lally. Estate property with extracts from Sir William's letter.
    - 25. 1786, June 21.New Broad St. John Fiott to Wm. Lee Antonie. Jermyn St. A.L.S. Sir John Warren's mortgage, Sir William's [Lee] business, picture: Death of Major Pierson.
    - 26. 1786, Nov. 7.London. John Fiott to Wm. Lee Antonie. Paris. A.L.S. journey, building ships, business - Medmenham Tythes.
    - 27. 1787, Aug. 10.London. John Fiott to Wm. Lee Antonie. Yarmouth. A.L.S. Mr. Delon, Sir Wm. Lee, Sir Robert Taylor - business.
    - 28. 1787, Aug. 11.London. John Fiott to Wm. Lee Antonie. Yarmouth. A.L.S. loss of the ship Hartwell, Capt. Fiott safe, in West Indies, mitiny the cause.
    - 29. 1787, Aug. 18.London. John Fiott to Wm. Lee Antonie. Yarmouth. A.L.S. hopes to build another ship, Marlow business, treaty?
    - 30. 1787, Dec. 1.London. John Fiott to Wm. Lee Antonie. Colworth House near Bedford. A.L.S. business, applications for Shrievalty of Bedfordshire.
    - 31. 1788, Jan. 5.London. John Fiott to Wm. Lee Antonie. Leicester. A.L.S. Sir John Dyke and Mr. Skynner.
    - 32. 1788, Jan. 16.London. John Fiott to Wm. Lee Antonie. Leicester. A.L.S. business, George [Lee?] is intended for the Church.
    - 33. 1792, Jan. 11.London. John Fiott to Wm. Lee Antonie. N.P. A.L.S. financial, Lord Boston.
    - 34. 1793, Jan. 31.London. John Fiott to Wm. Lee Antonie. Colworth House near Bedford. A.L.S. rival canals - The Grand Junction and the Western and London Navigation.
    - 35. 1794, Oct. 6.London. John Fiott to Wm. Lee Antonie. N.P. A.L.S. politics, dissolution of Parliament on the carpet, Sir Wm. Lee.
    - 36. 1795, Mar. 28.London. John Fiott to Wm. Lee Antonie. Colworth. A.L.S. Parliament, Mr. Fox's State of the Union, Landed Gentleman and Corporation of Lynn, drainage and navigation, death of Benton, properties.
    - 37. 1795, June 7.Totteridge. John Fiott to Wm. Lee Antonie, N.P. A.L.S. difficulty in raising money, Mr. Scott exchange of land Medmenham.
    - 38. 1795, Oct. 24.London. John Fiott to Wm. Lee Antonie. N.P. A.L.S. finances, Norfolk Estate, offer from Lord Grenville for part of Caybrook Estate.
    - 39. 1795, Dec. 15.London. John Fiott to Wm. Lee Antonie. N.P. A.L.S. death of Wm. Williams of Marlow, WLA's steward.
    - 40. 1795, Dec. 23.London. John Fiott to Wm. Lee Antonie. N.P. A.L.S. Mr. Williams affairs, Letter from Sir Wm. Lee critical of Wm. Lee Antonie, Parliament.
    - 41. 1796, Feb. 5.London. John Fiott to Wm. Lee Antonie. N.P. A.L.S. Edgeware Estate, Lynn Estate, Lord Greoville, Christie, Duke of Bedford, politics.
    - 42. 1796, Mar. 4.London. John Fiott to Wm. Lee Antonie. Colworth. A.L.S. shipping affairs at the India House - monopoly will meet its political death.
    - 43. 1796, Mar. 19.London. John Fiott to Wm. Lee Antonie. N.P. A.L.S. re: Wm. Lee Antonie's seat in Parliament, election campaign.
    - 44. 1796, July 22.London. John Fiott to Wm. Lee Antonie. Colworth. A.L.S. gambling by DeGruchy.
    - 45. 1796, July 23.London. John Fiott to Wm. Lee Antonie. Colworth. A.L.S. DeGruchy absented himself.
    - 46. 1796, Nov. 26.London. John Fiott to Wm. Lee Antonie. Colworth. A.L.S. Lynn Estate sale.
    - 47. 1796, Dec. 15.London. John Fiott to Wm. Lee Antonie. Colworth. A.L.S. Lynn Estaee.
    - 48. 1797, Jan. 4.London. John Fiott to Wm. Lee Antonie. Colworth. A.L.S. Norfolk Estate.
    - 49. 1787, Mar. 12.London. John Fiott to Wm. Lee. Strasbourg. A.L.S. book on inoculating for small pox.
    - 50. 1789, Nov. 3.London. [John Fiott] to Wm. Lee. Chichester. L. by J.P. DeGruchy - a painting, duty.
    - 51. [1790] Nov. 6.London. John Fiott to Wm. Lee. Hartwell. A.L.S. pictures from Custom House sale, prospect of raising a company.
    - 52. 1792, Nov. 16. _____port. John Fiott to Wm Lee. London. A.L.S. long absence.
    - 53. 1804, Aug. 31.St. Johns [Cambridge] John Fiott [Jr.?] to J.W. Hawksley. Souldrop near Bedford. A.L.S. lonely, college.
    - 54. 1805, Feb. 24.St. Johns [Cambridge] John Fiott [Jr.?] to J.W. Hawksley. Souldrop Mount. A.L.S. scholarship disputes, reading Newton.
    - 55. 1807, May 31.St. Johns [Cambridge] James Wood to J.W. Hawksley. Souldrop. A.L.S. re: a fellowship and Mr. Fiott.
    - 56. 1786, Nov. 16.London, J. Fozard to M. Lee. Strasbourg. A.L.S. sending books, Lee's cousin wounded a man in a duel.
    - 57. 1787, Aug. 11.London. J. Fozard to M. Lee. Strasbourg. A.L.S. darning needles.
    - 58. 1790, Aug. 23.London. J. Fozard to Wm. Lee. Maidstone. A.L.S. selling a horse.
    - 59. 1792, June 21.London. J. Fozard to Wm. Lee. Hartwell. A.L.S. sends horse, dog, etc.
    - 60. [1796] July 20.London. J. Fozard to Wm. Lee. Maidstone. A.L.S. sends watch.
    - 61. 1798, May 31.N.P. J. Fozard to [Lee] N.P. A.N.S. account.
    - 62. 1798, June 5.London. J. Fozard To Lt. Col. Lee. Guildford. A.L.S. horses, cost of boarding.
    - 63. [1798]N.P. J. Fozard to Lt. Col. Lee. Guildford. A.L.S. overdue account.
    - 64. 1800, Apr. 29.London. J. Fozard to Wm. Lee. Hartwell. A.L.S. reminder of money owed, Lee about to leave for India.
    - 65. N.D.London. J. Fozard to Wm. Lee. Chichester. A.L.S. servant.
    - 66. N.D.N.P. J. Fozard to Lt. Col. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. buying and selling horses.
  - G (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - 1. [1786?] Oct. 7.N.P. Steph. G_____ to Wm. Lee. N.P. A.D.S. receipt.
    - 2. 1786, May 21.Oldenburg. Gedelier to unknown. N.P. A.L.S. in French. statement re: two guns stolen or missing from house of J.E. Neumann while 16th Dragoons were quartered near.
    - 3. 1787, Mar. 6.London. Robert Gibson to M. Lee. Strasburgh. A.L.S. saddles sent.
    - 4. 1799, Mar. 14.London. Robert Gibson to Col. Lee. Windsor. A.L.S. bill.
    - 5. 1799, Mar. 19.London. Robert Gibson to Col. Lee. Windsor. A.L.S. bill.
    - 6. N.D., Dec. 20.Coventry. R[obert] Gibson to [Cornet] Lee. Cangerbury. A.L.S. re: payment of account.
    - 7. 1796, Sept. 10.London. Gibson son and Peat to Maj. Lee. Weymouth. sending bridle.
    - 8. 1798, Aug. 13.London. Gibson Son and Peat to Col. Lee. N.P. A.L. S. bill, father's illness.
    - 9. 1792, Jan. 12.[London] John Gilbert to Wm. Lee. Leighton. A.L.S. horses.
    - 10. 1792, Dec. 27.London. John Gilbert to Wm. Lee. Barnet. A.L.S. condition of mare.
    - 11. 1795, Nov. 20.Bremen. [F.] Gilchrist to Maj. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. financial, Sir Robert Laurie.
    - 12. 1796, Dec. 26.Reading. S. Goddard to Maj. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. condition of horse, Affleck.
    - 13. 1799, July 5.Maiden Early. Edward Golding to Lt. Col. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. re: a Sergeant.
    - 14. 1795, Mar. 19.Blackwall. John Goodwin to Maj. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. and return of Stores; orders of St. Ledger (fragile).
    - 15. 1801, Mar.___.N.P. _____ [Goparre] to Lt. Col. Lee. N.P. D.S. receipted bill.
    - 16-18. 1802, Sept 22.N.P. Goslings and Sharpe to Estate of Wm. Lee. 3 items: signed receipt to Estate trustees; bill and cover directed to Rose and [Munnings].
    - 19. 1791, Aug. 11.Newmarket. Edward Gould to Capt. Lee. Thetford. A.L.S. mare.
    - 20. 1780, May 18.Stone. Thomas Grace to Sir Wm. Lee, Bart. London. A.L.S. financial, Cleydon's Estate of Bishopstone.
    - 21. [1791] Jan. 17.N.P. _____ Grand Maison to Capt. Lee. Hartwell. A.L.S. in French. debt, sitting for portrait.
    - 22. 1791, Jan. 29.London. _____ Grand Maison to Capt. Lee. Hartwell. A.L.S. in French. threatened with arrest for debts to dressmaker, asks for help.
    - 23. [1791?] Feb. 2.N.P. _____ Grand Maison to Capt. Lee. Hartwell. A.L.S. in French. debt to dressmaker.
    - 24. 1791, Feb. 16.N.P. _____ Grand Maison to Capt. Lee. Heartwell. A.L.S. in French. personal, portrait.
    - 25. N.D.,N.P. _____ Grand Maison to Capt. Lee. Aylesbury. A.L. in French. invitation.
    - 26. 1801, Feb. 9.Fort George [India] W. Grant to Gen. Lake [Ft. George] A.L. Lee's will, Sir Thomas Strange.
    - 27. 1801, Feb. 10.Fort George [India] W. Grant. A.D.S. Opinion on Lee's will and procedure.
    - 28. 1797, Jan. 30.Buckingham. E. O. Gray to [lee?]. N.P. A.L.S. securing loan, mentions Grand Junction [canal]
    - 29. 1797, Nov. 3.London. [E.O. Gray] to Maj. [Lt. Col.] Wm. Lee. Guildford. A.L.S. by H. Phillips for Gray. thanks for remittance.
    - 30. 1798, Sept. 21.[London] F.N. [Greene] to Col. Lee. Windsor. A.L.S. does not expect financial help.
    - 31. 1756, Oct. 11.Brentford. _____ Robert Greening to [Wm. Lee III?] A.D.S. bill for hay and straw.
    - 32. 1799, July 10.London. Wm. Greenwollers to Lt. Col. Lee. Windsor. A.L.S. a bill drawn by George Lee.
    - 33. 1799, Nov. 6.London. Wm. Greenwollers to Mr. Chaplin, Atty. Aylesbury. A.L.S. writ against Wm. Lee.
    - 34. 1797, May 13.[Craigs Canal] Charles Greenwood to Maj. Lee. Beaconsfield. A.L.S. Lee's promotion to Lt. Col. approved but Majority must be filled before it can be announced.
    - 35. 1800, Jan. 20.N.P. John Gregory. A.D. Account of Wm. Lee.
    - 36. 1800, Nov. 22. Rockingham. [J. Grellier] to Capt. Butler. [Rockingham]. Copy of letter, denial of charges.
    - 37. 1800, Nov. 22. Rockingham. J. [Grellier] to Lt. Col. Lee. [Rockingham.] A.L.S. requests general court martial.
    - 38. 1796, Mar. ___[London] _____ Grenier to Mr. Lee. [London] A.L.S. in French. bill?
    - 39. 1797, [Sept?] 18.N.P. _____ Grenier to Maj. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. in French. bill.
    - 40. 1781, July 20.N.P. J. Griggs to Wm. Lee. Anylesbury. A.L.S. re: Cambridge, lessons, Lee an orator at Harrow.
    - 41. 1800, Apr. 9.Veterinary College. J. Gullier to Col. Lee. London. A.L.S. passage to East India.
    - 42. 1800, Apr. 28.Lincoln's Inn. J. Gullier to Col. Lee. [Hartwell] A.L.S. wants to sail with Lee, Gen. Hewet.
    - 43. 1797, Feb. 18.King's Mews. [Maj. Gen. Gwyn] to Maj. Lee. Reading. A.L.S. by Henry Edward Bunbury.
      re: a horse, regiment quarters.
  - GARDEN, GARDNER (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - 1. 1790, Nov. 11.London. J. Garden to Capt. Lee. Hartwell. A.L.S. military equipment and clothing.
    - 2. 1790, Jan. 22.London. H.H. Gardner to Lee. N.P. A.L.S. paid draft, looking for snuff box, gold rings, to write to Harcourt about a horse, mentions Pitt.
    - 3. 1792, July 2.Barracks Up-park [West Indies?]. H.H. Gardner to Lt. Lee. London. A.L.S. barracks, etc., horses, troops, Anson, eating turtle, we all have fine young handsome brown girls, slave bill, Negroes, Cornwallis, Curacao, war with Spain reported, business on the Cape, French troops, Blanchelard, Black Commander, earthquake, reinstate Colony?
    - 4 & 5. N.D.NPP. [Gardner] to Cornet Lee, Chichester. two covers.
    - 6. N.D.N.P. H.H. Gardner to Cornet Lee. Chichester. A.N.S. in French - invitation.
    - 7. N.D., Dec. 28.Fareham. H.H. Gardner to Cornet Lee. [Canterbury?] A.L.S. horse, pistols, asks about Cangerbury, mentions Earl Derby.
    - 8. N.D.Grosvenor Square. H.H. Gardner to Cornet Lee. Lewes. A.L.S. watch repair, recruit horses, Lee to act as commanding officer, Lrrd Derby going to Newmarket.
    - 9. N.D., Sept. 4.Chichester. H.H. Gardner to Cornet Lee. Lewes. A.L.S. Gen. Harcourt growing impatient. Mr. Shelly. Lewes sheep fair, orders sheep for Gen. Harcourt.
    - 10. N.D.Petworth. H.H. Gardner to Lee. N.P. A.L.S. horses, Sir Harry Featherstone and Count Bfuhl.
    - 11. N.D.Grosvenor Square. H.H. Gardner to Lee. N.P. A.L.S. pheasants, troop horses.
    - 12. N.D., Feb. 29.Grosvenor Square. H.H. Gardner to Lee. N.P. A.L.S. illness.
    - 13. N.D.,N.P. H.H. Gardner to Lee. [Canterbury?] A.L.S. Sir Robert, horses, personal, free mason?
    - 14. N.D.Up Park. H.H. Gardner to Lee. N.P. A.L.S. boxing match.
    - 15. N.D.London. H.H. Gardner to Lee. N.P. A.L.S. unexpected arrival of Prince Edward, stag hunting.
  - H (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - 1. 1785, Oct. 28.London. T. Hall. to [Wm. Lee] N.P. A.L.S. advancing money, to sell horse.
    - 2. 1785, Nov. 19.London. T. Hall to Cornet Lee. Canterbury. A.L.S. terrier, finances.
    - 3. 1799, May 23.Canterbury. H.D. Hamilton to [Wm. Lee] N.P. A.L.S. rumor that Lee wants to quit Service.
    - 4. [1800]N.D. Monday 4 o'clock. N.P. R. Harding to Wm. Lee. South Hampton. A.L.S. proceeding to Portsmouth.
    - 5. [1800]Monday. N.P. R. Harding to Wm. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. R.Harding and Capt. Craig regret they will not have Lee's company.
    - 6. [1800]N.D. Saturday. N.P. Richard Harding to Sir Wm. Lee. [London] A.L.S. India House, despatches, sudden departure from Town.
    - 7. 1785, Sept. 15.London. J.R. Harrington to [Wm. Lee] N.P. A.L.S. life insurance.
    - 8. 1785, Sept. 15.London. J.R. Harrington to Capt. Lee. Present A.L.S. life insurance, different from above.
    - 9. 1797, June 30.War Office. James Harrington to Col. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. irregular newspaper delivery.
    - 10. 1797, Oct. 2.War Office. James Harrington to Col. Lee. N.P. A.L.S.
    - 11. 1797, Oct. 28.War Office. James Harrington to Col. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. newspaper delivery.
    - 12. 1799, Nov. 4.[London] Wm. Harris to Wm. Lee. Hartwell. A.L.S. jewelry.
    - 13. 1798, Oct. 22.[London?] J. Harrison to Lt. Col. Lee. Windsor. A.L.S. black pony.
    - 14. 1798, Dec. 17.[London?] J. Harrison to Col. Lee. Windsor. A.L.S. brown horse.
    - 15 & 16. 1759, Jan. 23.[Hursby] Thomas Heathcote to Sir Wm. Lee (III). [London] A.L.S. have to let the House to Mr. Secretary Pitt, and document re: rental details (not signed).
    - 17. 1795, May 29.Oldenburg. Hemdorf Herbert to unknown. A.L.S. police unable to find 2 lost guns.
    - 18. 1792, Feb. 3.London. Robert Herries to Wm. Lee. Thetford. A.L.S. financial.
    - 19 & 20. 1800, Apr. 7.Chatham. [J.] Hewitt to Lt. Col. Lee. London. A.L.S. and cover. embarking soldiers.
    - 21. 1798, May 17.Clapham. C.L. [Hisse] to Lt. Col. Lee. Guildford. A.L.S. horse.
    - A. 1796, Dec. 29.London. Charles Hompesch to [Major Lee] ... The infantry is under sailing order for the barbados
    - B. 1797, Jan. 8.London. Hompesch to major [Lee], Henley
      re: purchase of Dr. Coley for Lee then to germany or Portugal
    - C. 1797, Jan. 14.London. Charles Hompesch to [major Lee], Henley.
      re: commission
    - D. 1797, Jan. 15.London. Charles Hompesch to [major] Lee. Henley re: commission
    - E. 1797, Jan. 26.Chester Place, Combeth. Charles Hompesch to Major [Lee] Henley. re: sale of majority
    - F. 1797, April 24.London. Charles Hompesch to Lee Beaconsfield
      re: Claitons complaints...The trial comes forth in a few days...
    - G. N.D., Feb. 7.London. Charles Hompesch to major [Lee]. Henley.
    - H. N.D., Feb. 10.London. Charles Hompesch to major [Lee] Henley. re: commission
    - I. N.D., March 3.N.P. Charles Hompesch to Lee Henley. ... genl. Harcourt seems to be The chief obstacle
    - J. N.D., Sunday 5thLondon. Hompesch to Lee. Beaconsfield
      re: Nesbitt's attitude toward sale of Lee's majority
    - K. N.D., Sunday 19thLondon. Charles Hompesch to major [Lee] Henley re: commision
    - L. N.D., 10thLondon. Charles Hompesch to majro [Lee] N.P.
    - M. N.D.,London. Charles Hompesch to Lee. Henley I have been duing my good friend... you may have my Lieut. Coley..."
    - N. N.D.Maidenshead. Hompesch to Major [Lee] Reading or Ockenham
    - O. N.D.Maidenshead. Hompesch to major [Lee] N.P.
    - P. N.D.London. Charles Hompesch ot Lee. Beaconsfield mention Prince of wales
    - Q. N.D. 16thLondon. Charles Hompesch to Lee
    - R. N.D.Sunday evening. Maidenshead. Charles Hompesch to major Lee N.P. re: french invasion of ingland-I myself... wish That These terrible french should come as far as Madenhorn... to have a few shots at them...
    - 22. 1785, July 2.N.P. J. Hopkins to Cornet Lee. Maidstone. A.L.S. horses, account.
    - 23. 1785, July 9.London. J. Hopkins to Cornet Lee. Maidstone. A.L.S. bill.
    - 24. 1785, Aug. 15.London. J. Hopkins to Cornet Lee. Maidstone. A.L.S. horse.
    - 25. [1787] Feb. 9.Southampton Row. Job Horne to Lee. Canterbury. A.L.S. servant.
    - 26. 1787, Feb. 18.(place illegible) Job Horne to [Lee] N.P. A.L.S. money.
    - 27. 1787, June 23.London. James Humphrey to M. Lee. Strasbourg. A.L.S. Humphrey's dead brother's finances, claim against Lee.
    - 28. 1787, July 14.Paris. James Hunt to M. Lee. Strasbourg. A.L.S. French lessons, prepairing to serve Lee, Capt. Vassar, Mr. Wood.
    - 29a. 1788, May 20.Brunswick. James Hunt to Wm. Lee. Magdebourg. A.L.S. unable to send things to Berlin, disagreeable journey, little dog has one bad eye.
    - 29b. 1788, July 16.Magdebourg. James Hunt to M. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. legal matter involving Lee, lawyer wants information, change lodgings, has dogs and fox.
    - 30a. 1788, July 20.Magdebourg. James Hunt to Wm. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. Lee's departure, personal, Germans, fair.
    - 31. [1794] Dec. 3.N.P. G. Orby Hunter to Maj. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. wonders why his conduct is suspect.
    - 32. 1795, Jan. 2.London. G. Orby Hunter. to [Lee?] N.P. A.L.S. sudden departure from 16th Lt. Dragoons, why he quit Fusiliers.
    - 33. 1795, Jan. 16.[London] G. Orby Hunter to Maj. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. drunk at theatre, fight with Munroe in Glasgow.
    - 34. 1790, Jan.[G. Orby Hunter] Copies of letters enclosed in #33.
    - 35. 1801, Feb. 8.N.P. Cornet Hutchinson to Lt. Col. Lee (or estate). A.D.S. bill.
  - HAWKER, HUMPHREYS (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - 1. 1791, Oct. 26.Lynn. Samuel Hawker to Lt. Lee. Thetford. A.L.S. greyhounds, racing, Harcourt.
    - 2. 1796, Feb. 4.On board the Winchester Transport. Samuel Hawker to Maj. Lee. On board the Prince of Wales Transport. A.L.S. re: horse collars, etc.
    - 3. 1796, Feb. 4.On board the Winchester Transport, Samuel Hawker. A.D.S. Certifies that 17 ship collars for horses are unfit for service.
    - 4. 1796, Feb. 4.On board the Winchester Transport. Samuel Hawker. A.D.S. Certifies need for more candles.
    - 5. 5. 1796, Feb. 4.On board the Winchester Transport. Samuel Hawker. A.D.S. Certifies need of sheepskins for protection of horses.
    - 6. 1796, Mar. 11.Reading. Samuel Hawker to Maj. Lee. Hampstead. A.L.S. has been subpoena'd to appear at a trial at Salisbury, recruits.
    - 7. 1796, Aug. 2.Weymouth. Samuel Hawker to [Lee] N.P. Ryan of 15th wants Lee's Majority, Lord Paget and Affleck, griping, Le Marchant, Dundas, Tudor, the King arrived yesterday - fell on his (King) back in rain during inspection, etc.
    - 8a. 1799, May 18.Hampton Court. Samuel Hawker to Lt. Col. Lee. [London] A.L.S. plan at Hounslow Barracks to murder Stone, Affleck and Burnet.
    - 8b. 1799, May 18.Hampton Court. Samuel Hawker to Lt. Col. Lee. Windsor. A.L.S. plan to murder Stone, Affleck and Burnet by troops at Hounslow, to set fire to barracks.
    - 9. N.D.[B_____?] Samuel Hawker to Cornet Lee. Canterbury. A.L.S. asks favor.
    - 10. N.D. N.P. Samuel Hawker to Lt. Lee, Thetford. A.L.S. Denis, Naissen, horses, Sir Robert Laurie.
    - 11. N.D. N.P. Samuel Hawker to Lt. Lee. Thetford. A.L.S. illnesses, Hawker's face swollen.
    - 12. 1786, Aug. 15.N.P. Thomas Humphreys to Wm. Lee. Hartwell. A.L.S. finances and personal.
    - 13. 1786, Sept. 1.London. Thomas Humphreys to Wm. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. financial, watches, going to Rochester.
    - 14. 1786, Sept. 12.[London] Thomas Humphreys to Wm. Lee. Hartwell. A.L.S. Mrs. Baker and her Company at Tunbridge, mentions Sir William and my Lady.